Cousin, this place is pretty big.
I wonder where exactly the Dragon-Seeking Ruler is hidden.
No matter where it's hidden,
it must be
waiting for our arrival.
Cousin, you're amazing!
Of course. Unlike some people,
who have no clue where Funerary objects are placed.
Well, I still get to be the Sheng family's son-in-law.
You...
Enough. Let's go.
Slow down.
Honestly, cousin,
if we weren't accompanying you on your first geomancy trip,
to a small place like this,
my brother wouldn't even bother coming himself.
Look at this!
Bringing this loser along is just bad luck.
Even the coffin we found is a miniature version.
Rat,
get to work.
We need to pry it open.
Hold on.
Something doesn't seem right about this thing.
Ling Yu,
bring out the treasure yourself.
Cousin!
Don't be scared. Cousin is here, everything's fine.
This coffin is just one layer, the Outer coffin.
This Earthenware urn is the real coffin.
Ling Yu.
Something's wrong with this thing.
What do you know, you jinx?
It's fine, cousin.
Go ahead and open it.
We've got our brother's overlord aura protecting us.
Who?
Who touched me?
What is it now?
Brother!
A hand just touched me from behind.
Young Master Qi.
Using an Earthenware urn as a coffin usually suppresses monsters.
I don't think we should let Ling Yu take the risk.
What do you mean?
You don't want Ling Yu to open the coffin?
Are you just eager to take the credit for yourself?
I've got the Qi Family's Corpse-Suppressing Talisman on it.
Don't worry, just reach in.
Who? Who? Who?
Who touched me again?
Can you stop being so jumpy in a place like this?
Acting all paranoid.
It's nothing. Come on.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Ling Yu?
A little hand grabbed me and won't let go!
What little hand?
It's alright. You're fine.
Are you alright?
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
Get up!
They're raising an Imp in this urn!
Smash the urn and save her!
You think I don't know how to smash it?
I don't need you to tell me!
Why isn't it working?!
It's like reinforced concrete!
Get up!
Tianyou, save me!
What is that thing?
The Dragon-Seeking Ruler isn't here.
Zhang Tianyou!
How did you do that just now?
I don't know either.
I just felt like...
it was about to break.
Stop bragging.
I obviously hit it so many times,
and you just lightly touched it at the end
and it broke.
Right, right, right.
He broke it, he broke it.
Brother!
What is this?
What is that thing?
What is that thing?!
Don't worry.
Our Qi family still has Life-saving talismans.
Look, better now?
I have more.
I have plenty more talismans.
They can all save our lives.
One for you.
I'll stick one on too.
One for me.
One for you, one for me.
One for you, one for me, one for you.
Another one for you, another one for me.
Young Master Qi, stop sticking them.
Put two on your brother.
What happened to him?
Even his hairstyle changed.
Madam, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
Could it be...
a Talisman Alert?
Things look grim.
This is bad!
I'm—
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
It's okay.
Cousin is here.
It's okay. It's okay, it's okay.